All
right good morning good afternoon and
good evening
because I don't know what time you're
watching this video but thank you
so much
for the time you took to
watch this will help you a lot and
we are here to explain or I am here
to explain the importance of my
insurance the benefits of my
insurance
and By the way I'm debora
campanero I am a licensed financial
wealth
Planner of fwd insurance and so
I want to share with you
the beauty
of fw insurance fwd insurance Okay so
if we see what
fwd means we might think that forward is
the meaning of fwd But it is
Chinese characters that mean
F is
fo meaning wealth or riches and it
represents prosperity and abundance
The w is for
way that means guard or defend and it is
often associated with safeguarding or
protection and the D is for
the that means Uh achieve or attain it
signifies Reaching a goal or being
accomplished So fua that's what it
means and Of course since insurance
we want to um
secure your finances
wealth and our goals in life
so let me just give you a short
background about
fwd Okay so fwd is the insurance
business of investment group the
Pacific Century group so this is just one of the
Galamay of the Pacific Century group
you can search on the internet how
big this Pacific Century group is
considered by investors
businessmen so fwd is very Secure
also it was established in 2013 and
Began in or in the Philippines in 2014
so it started in 2014 in the Philippines
But of course it was established in 2013
since it is under the Pacific Century
group and if we notice Mr Lee is the
founder so he is from
Hong Kong next
fwd life insurance rank number 3 in the
MD rt rankings among insurance companies
in the philippines so you will notice
that it only started in 2014 in the Philippines
so we are still 2 14 now it is still 10
years old and you will see
the speed of its rise '
we are in the top three immediately in the market So it means
the company is good the service is good and
our offers So now the MDRT
is a million dollar Round Table so
the premier Association of financial
professionals MDRT is a prestigious
award given to the top 2% of financial
planners worldwide We always attend
MDRT so that's the short background of
FWD and you can see that on the internet
That's why we immediately made the top three
Actually we were honored as
number one in customer experience among
insurance brands So um there are many
great insurance
companies but we made number one
we got number one in customer
experience Because
the company and the offers and
more products are good as well as the service that
financial advisors or financial wealth
planners how do they
help the clients Okay so
we are also fast in the process because we are digital
we can um we can
ensure a client through a
digital process only so it's
really fast So even if he is in a faraway place
we can ensure him
As long as the processes are done so That's when
we look at what
we should
insure in our lives Why do
we need insurance because when
we say insurance it means security and
this is our advocacy
Every
Filipino should be Secure Because if we look at
us
Filipinos, it seems like we don't have the
security thing because we are It seems okay I'm okay
now I'm alive now this is
okay that's all we are but we don't
think about the future Only a few
Filipinos really think
about their future
and that's what hurts because other countries
really prioritize the
future when they get sick when
they lose
their family They are also secure
when it comes to finances and
health So for us Filipinos it seems like
we forget that thing that
we should prioritize and
really pay attention to So that's what
we want to pay attention to For
that, educate every
Filipino about the importance
and the good benefits of
insurance So Where should we secure
ourselves and our
family first of all in our
finances So Do we have savings
Where do we save our money
because Filipinos often have jobs
but almost nothing is saved If
they save in the bank, they just leave it
in the bank but
the bank doesn't return any interest because  The
bank's profit is really small so that's what
we want to solve if
you put your money in insurance you will
really have savings Why can't you
withdraw it immediately because that is
for future use unlike in the bank you can get it right
away That's why it doesn't
grow 'ba So if for example you saved
10 36,000 ah throughout that year that's
still what you can take out it won't
grow unlike insurance when
you are insured you can also insure your health
why because when a client gets sick
okay the one who applied
he has something to use for
his illness when he suddenly had a
critical illness he had
cancer he has money to get to
cover his
medical expenses so that's one thing health is
very important because almost
everyone is going through illness 'ba So that's
important important or for example
we have a family we have
children it's also important that we save
for their future so that
they can graduate securely so if
you have insurance that's going to school you can go to school
and be
covered
if we also have insurance because
when we enter our  money from the
insurance company
um we have something called living
benefits that means let's say two
types of insurance can be
traditional and also what is called
vul which is the
money you put into stocks is put in so
it grows because it has interest eh
It grows every year that's what um
we get living benefits while
we are still alive we can withdraw
when our money matures Okay so
let's see how insurance works
suppose Ah Mark then Anna there are two of
them Mark he saves in the bank so
he saves 3,000 every month in the
bank so in 12 months it will be
only 36,000 plus the interest
That's what I told you even if
you search there is almost no interest to be earned
or nothing can be added to your 36,000 for the
whole year so Mark will still get
36,000 unlike Anna he put it
in fwd insurance for example since
Anna puts her money in stocks
then her 3,000 every month that is being
put into insurance she will get in 12
months to be 36,000 but it's good
here when something bad happens to
Anna like she gets a critical
illness she has an emergency fund that
can get 1 million It depends on her
on the insurance she took So if
she has it for critical illness
she can get 1 million or then
she still has a death benefit that can be
given to her family if
she passes away at least
her family won't be left in
tears 'cause they won't be left
full of debt so Anna was wise in
choosing how to save
her money because she is secured by what
she did she is secured by
emergency things like if she gets
sick when she passes away
she will have a benefit because it
was put in her insurance Okay so that's the
difference between the two of them and Mark
now I want to show you the
summary of benefits premiums and
insurance charges Okay so this is
I just took it from one of my
um ah clients and this is what he
pays 2.8
8.46 every month Okay so this is just the
monthly benefit that he gives but  let
's look at the benefits there are here we also have
this benefit description there is some
assured the some assured this is what
the family will get in case
my client dies Ah the
benefit period Until when will he
benefit from these and then the
initial insurance charges payment period
and total annual premium so what
he took was what was entered in the
stocks Okay so what he took was the set
for life whole life pay death benefit so
what this means is continuous
savings he saves continually
until he lives and there is
some assured 2 million So if ever
he dies
his family will get 2 million so it's
clean that it will go to them and
his benefit period is up to age 100
Okay so he can live until 100
Until then he is still insured then
he has added something he
also took health Pro this is the addition
we say in his benefits
health Pro when you are in agga he
had a critical illness
he will get 400,000 immediately like say he
had
cancer he will get  400,000
then the following year he got
another critical illness Okay
he got Diabetes another 400,000
then another year another
critical illness
he will get another 400,000 So if
we have one he immediately got 1.2 million
if it is a different illness because
the fwd gives up to three
times claim of critical illness and that
is up to age 60 so there he also
took safety Pro which is
100,000 when he has an
accident and dies so it will
affect his family there will be an
additional
100,000 Okay up to age 75 that is
until he is 75 and then in
recovery Pro This is when
he is confined and gets sick
for example let's say he is confined
he has 100 is Php1,000 per day but
our minimum here is that he must be confined
for 3 days so he can claim 3 days and
Above 3 days up Okay so if  He was confined
for 5 days, 10 days, he will get
the 1,000 benefit per
day. Okay, so he is that beautiful if
you can see him. It's terrible.
You only pay 2838 every
month, but the benefits that
his family and he will get are
huge. So what else are you looking for? What
else do you need to work hard for
if the benefits
you will get are like this? Secure your family
in case you
lose it or that's the client. So that's
why I did what I did. I
immediately got a job. I immediately got two
insurance policies because I don't want what happened
to
us before to happen to me again, begging because
my mother didn't have insurance, so
my father didn't have a job.
We didn't have anything to eat and we were begging. We
borrowed a lot. That's what
degrades our
dignity. So I said that this won't
happen to me and us again. So
I really got two insurance policies
to make sure that I won't be a burden
to my family. So now I want to
show you the
living benefits. We said that
when the weather is bad,  What you took is putting the
money you put into stocks now
there is what is called total living
benefits that has benefits because it is put
into stocks now our example is Rico
ah He entered when he was 39 years old So
this is the policy year his payment
How many years for example here and
now and this is the total living benefits
ah in the Market because when you put that into
stocks ah there are three possible ones that you can
choose from It depends on the
economy with inflation supposedly only 4%
when the economy is very low
88% 10% so these are the sure ones This is the only one that
ah really gives
Okay so sometimes it increases even more
More than 10 but this is the only sure one that
we want to show
you that is sure that can be obtained It depends
on the economy So now in the 10th year of
Rico's payment he is 48 years old
So if we look at how much
he earned at
10% His money earned is
168000 222
so here he can take here
50,000 can be withdrawn, it's withdrawable,
so he can get 50,000 to
start a business, as long as you don't use it
up because if you use it up,
your insurance will also be lost, so
we advise you not to take it all out or not to
withdraw it all out so that
your insurance stays, okay? So by the age of 58,
he already has
629,451. What if he doesn't want to take
it? He wants to be around 65,
so he already has
1,308,639.
So it depends on when you
want to withdraw it, if you're
just a little bit crazy, just don't use it up.
Okay, that's how good insurance is
because you're really sure that you'll save up something. And
if, for example, your child
has a child in his first year,
he's 39 years old, or in his 10th
year, he can go to
college. Or if his child is
still 18 years old, or if his child is 18, he'll
go to college when he's 18 years old.  He already has Or
he already has 499
961 So he can get a
job here, isn't the insurance that good?
That's why it's like that. Ah,
our desire is to educate every
Filipino for that, so that he doesn't
suffer or they don't have problems in the
future because if we invest in what,
I'll buy land first, I'll buy
a car first. What if you lose your
job? What if you get sick,
you'll lose your
job, no one will come into that money.
You still got what you invested because
you just sold it because you don't have
insurance that can be used
for paying
your hospital bills. So that's what we want to
see or show every Filipino.
If we look at almost all
rich countries, almost everyone there has
insurance. In America, in Singapore, they're
lining up insurance companies.
The Japanese don't, they don't, they don't, they
only take one insurance, up to six
or seven insurances, I think
they take it to be really sure that they won't have any
problems even if they
retire early. They have money,
their health is secured.
ah future So I hope that we Filipinos will
also think about it because it is really
important
So now I just want to leave some
other questions or questions
to ponder for us the question is have you saved
or are you saving anything '
ba Is there anything left in your salary or is
your money just going out all the time 'ba
Let's think about when we were young L an the
children who started working it's
good that they are saving now because the
insurance they can get is a little lower
or is what you are saving short term or long term 'ba It's
better if it's long term
in case something
bad happens SAO if you get sick with a
critical illness you can't
work you have an accident
for example or pass away We don't
ask for that but there are possibilities like
that and we don't know Won't you
leave or leave your family with debt or
money problems do we think about
the good if we think about it now
and prepare because we won't either ah
end up getting sick 'ba
When we get old do we want to grow
old without saving at all and
Just rely on your parents, right?
It's like the elderly don't like them,
their children don't like their grandchildren, because that's just the way it is, so
hopefully that won't
happen to us, so do you think
this insurance will help you and your family, or if yes, are you willing to
set aside a portion of your money to
ensure that you and
your family aren't miserable one day? These are the things
I thought about right away when
we first experienced that
with our mother. We were at a loss,
we loved our mother very much,
but she was still gone, because
you know that, and then we couldn't give
her anything, we didn't have insurance, she didn't have
insurance, so we were really in trouble. So that's why
I really told myself
that it shouldn't be like this, that this won't
happen to us anymore. So now I hope
you realize that, and Uh,
and pay attention right away because
we don't know when we'll get sick, when we'll have an
accident,
or if we'll pass away, but it's
better to always be prepared so that
we don't regret it one day. Okay, so
if you're willing,
I'm here. You can
contact me, okay.  so thank you so much and
may God bless you and keep you